A Guide to the Correspondence and subject files of the Chancellor of the Virginia Community College System, 1964-2012
Library of Virginia
- Series I: Correspondence and subject files [Accession 31048], 1973-1978., Extent: 34 cu. ft. (34 boxes). (Box 1-34)
  - Subseries B. 1977
    - Christopher Newport College's transfer policies and credit evaluation (Box 16)
    - The Chronicle of Higher Education, Publication (Box 16)
    - Classification of students (Box 16)
    - Coal and Energy Research Board (Box 16)
    - The College Board News (Box 16)
    - College and University Bulletin, Publication (Box 16)
    - College calendar (Box 16)
    - College Entrance Examination Board (Box 16)
    - Collegiate Registrars and Admissions Officers meeting (Box 16)
    - Commerce, U.S. Dept. of (Box 16)
    - Commission of the Needs of Elderly Virginians (Box 16)
    - Community and Junior Colleges, State legislation affecting (Box 17)
    - Community College Review Editorial Board meeting (Denver, Co.) (Box 17)
    - Community College Review Editorial Board (Box 17)
    - Community College System, Research (Box 17)
    - Community College Presidents names and addresses (Box 17)
    - Commonwealth, Secretary of (Box 17)
    - Community College Review, Publication (Box 17)
    - Community Colleges of Virginia Educational Foundation, Inc. (Box 17)
    - Community and Junior College Journal (Box 17)
    - Compact, Publication (Box 17)
    - CETA (Comprehensive Education Training Act) (Box 17)
    - Computer Center, VCU, VCCCS (Box 17)
    - Data Center meeting (Box 17)
    - Congress of the United States (Box 17)
    - Congressional Committees (Box 17)
    - Congressional Districts (Box 17)
    - Consortium for Higher Education Northern Virginia (Box 17)
    - Constitution, Virginia Association of Community College Faculty (Box 17)
    - Construction progress report (Box 17)
    - Construction financing (Box 17)
    - Construction, Temporary facilities (Box 17)
    - Consultants (Box 17)
    - Contracts (Box 17)
    - Comptroller, Office of the (Box 17)
    - Computer (Box 17)
    - The Coop Bulletin, Publication (Box 17)
    - Copyrighting (Box 17)
    - Corrections, Dept. of. (Box 17)
    - Continuing Education, Division of (Box 17)
    - COPA, Task Force on Educational Quality (Box 17)
    - Creighton, Sam, Travel schedule (Box 17)
    - Creighton, Sam, Miscellaneous (Box 17)
    - Creighton, Sam, Miscellaneous (Box 17)
    - Credit Bureau of Richmond (Box 17)
    - Cultural Laureate Center (Box 17)
    - D, Miscellaneous (Box 17)
    - Deans of Instruction, Advisory Committee (Box 17)
    - Deans meeting (Box 17)
    - Delaware Technical and Community College (Box 17)
    - Duplicating (Box 17)
    - E, Miscellaneous (Box 17)
    - Eastern Virginia Medical Authority (Box 17)
    - Economic Development Administration (Box 17)
    - Editorial Review Board (Box 17)
    - Education Commission of the States (Box 17)
    - Education, U.S. Office of (Box 17)
    - Educational Advisory Committee, Certification of Alcoholism Counselors (Box 17)
    - Educational Computing, Advisory Council for (Box 17)
    - Educational Foundation (Box 17)
    - Educational Programs Division (Box 17)
    - Economic Development Administration (Box 17)
    - Elder, Personnel (Box 17)
    - Emergency Services, State Office of (Box 17)
    - Community Colleges, Various, MBO (Management by Objectives) Plans (Box 17)
    - Energy crisis (Box 18)
    - Energy Office, Virginia (Box 18)
    - Engineering Technology Program, Discontinuance of (Box 18)
    - Enrollments, Misc. (Box 18)
    - Enrollments, 1977-1978 (Box 18)
    - Enrollments, 1976-1978 (Box 18)
    - Enrollments, 1976-1977 (Box 18)
    - Enrollments, 1975-1978 (Box 18)
    - Enrollments, 1975-1984 (Box 18)
    - Enrollments, 1974-1976 (Box 18)
    - Enrollments, 1970-1971, 1979-1980 (Box 18)
    - Enrollment Coordinators (Box 18)
    - Enrollment projections (Box 18)
    - Enrollments, Fall quarter 1978 (Box 18)
    - Enrollment forms (Box 18)
    - Enrollments, 1977 (Box 18)
    - Energy alternatives (Box 18)
    - Environment, Council on the (Box 18)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity (Box 18)
    - ERIC Clearinghouse for Junior Colleges (Box 18)
    - Executive Committee and Industrial Development meeting (Box 18)
    - Executive Order #52 (Box 18)
    - Executive Officers Association (Box 18)
    - Executive Support Center (Box 18)
    - Executive Support Center (Box 18)
    - Executive Support Center (Box 18)
    - Expenditures, Fiscal year 1976-1977 (Box 18)
    - Expenditure object (Box 18)
    - F, Miscellaneous (Box 18)
    - Faculty Advisory Committee, Proceedings Record file (Box 18)
    - Faculty Advisory Committee, Meeting (Box 18)
    - Faculty Association (Box 18)
    - Faculty, Evaluation plans (Box 18)
    - Faculty, Miscellaneous (Box 18)
    - Faculty, Salaries (Box 18)
    - Federal Funds (Box 18)
    - Federal Monies (Box 18)
    - Federal Programs (Box 18)
    - Federal Surplus Property (Box 18)
    - Federal Trade Commission (Box 18)
    - Finance, Other States (Box 18)
    - Financial statements (Box 18)
    - Facilities Planning and Engineering (Box 18)
    - Flood Relief Program (Box 18)
    - Florida State University (Box 18)
    - Ford Foundation Regionalism Project (Box 18)
    - Ford, Andrew T., N.H. College and University (Box 18)
    - Forms Management Program (Box 18)
    - Forum Club (Box 19)
    - G, Miscellaneous (Box 19)
    - Galanti, Commander Paul E. (Box 19)
    - General Assembly (Box 19)
    - General Assembly (Box 19)
    - Golden Wings Over Richmond (Box 19)
    - Grades and grading (Box 19)
    - Graduates profile (Box 19)
    - Graduates, Survey (Box 19)
    - Graduation requirements (Box 19)
    - Grants procedure (Box 19)
    - Hamel, Dr., Automobile (Box 19)
    - Hamel, Dr., Travel (Box 19)
    - Handicapped persons (Box 19)
    - Harris, John (Box 19)
    - Harris, William O. (Box 19)
    - Health, Dept. of (Box 19)
    - Health, Education, and Welfare (Box 19)
    - Monthly reports from Deputy Chancellor Counsel (Box 19)
    - Health and Medical Care, Council of (Box 19)
    - Health programs (Box 19)
    - Heating Plant Analysis (Box 19)
    - Henrico County (Box 19)
    - Higher Education Act of 1965 (Box 19)
    - Highway Safety Division (Box 19)
    - Hopper Plan (Box 19)
    - House Document #12 (Box 19)
    - Human Resources research organization (Box 19)
    - I, Miscellaneous (Box 19)
    - Instructional Programs Advisory Committee (Box 19)
    - Insurance (Box 19)
    - Issues of state-wide significance (Box 19)
    - Intergovernmental affairs (Box 19)
    - Virginia State Agencies' Sub-State Districts and Regional Planning Areas report (Box 19)
    - Invitations (Box 19)
    - Invitation list for ground breaking (Box 19)
    - Industrial Development, Division of (Box 19)
    - IBM (Box 19)
    - Instructional Media Materials Resource Center (Box 19)
    - Invoices (Box 19)
    - J, Miscellaneous (Box 19)
    - JLARC, Land Study (Box 19)
    - JLARC (Box 20)
    - JLARC (Box 20)
    - K, Miscellaneous (Box 20)
    - Kiplinger Washington Letter weekly (Box 20)
    - L, Miscellaneous (Box 20)
    - L-1 Enrollments (Box 20)
    - Land, state owned (Box 20)
    - Legal matters (Box 20)
    - Legislative Services, Division of (Box 20)
    - Loans, Students (Box 20)
    - M, Miscellaneous (Box 20)
    - Mail room (Box 20)
    - Malone, Dumas (Box 20)
    - Management Analysis and Systems Development, Dept. (Box 20)
    - Merritt, Dr. Johnnie E. (Box 20)
    - Merritt, Dr. Johnnie E. (Box 20)
    - Michigan State University (Box 20)
    - Military personnel (Box 20)
    - Minority Business, Va. State Office of (Box 20)
    - Miscellaneous file folders (Box 20)
    - Management Manpower Assessment Survey (Box 20)
    - Management Manpower Assessment Survey (Box 20)
    - Management-By-Objective Task Force (Box 20)
    - MIS (Management Information System) (Box 20)
    - MIS (Management Information System) (Box 20)
    - Management Development Training Services (Box 20)
    - Management services (Box 20)
    - Map, VCCS (Box 20)
    - Mary Washington College (Box 20)
    - Manpower, Federal training (Box 20)
    - Manpower Services Council, Governor's (Box 20)
    - Martorana, Dr. S.V. (Box 20)
    - Media Systems Corporation (Box 20)
    - Management Services (Box 20)
    - Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Dept. of (Box 20)
    - Miscellaneous publications (Box 20)
    - Monographs, Community College (Box 21)
    - N, Miscellaneous (Box 21)
    - National Science Foundation (Box 21)
    - National Guard (Box 21)
    - National Education Association (Box 21)
    - National Council of State Directors' meeting (Box 21)
    - National Advisory Council on Extension and Continuing Education (Box 21)
    - National Council of State Directors of Community and Junior Colleges (Box 21)
    - Navy recruiting (Box 21)
    - Newspaper articles (Box 21)
    - Newspaper articles (Box 21)
    - Newsletter for the System (Box 21)
    - Network trainers (Box 21)
    - New Jersey Community Colleges Publication (Box 21)
    - Nursing, State Board of (Box 21)
    - North Carolina State University (Box 21)
    - Nova University (Box 21)
    - Norfolk State College (Box 21)
    - O, Miscellaneous (Box 21)
    - Off-campus offerings (Box 21)
    - Old Dominion University (Box 21)
    - Optometry (Box 21)
    - P, Miscellaneous (Box 21)
    - Palmer, Dr. Charles E. (Box 21)
    - Payment authorization (Box 21)
    - Payroll (Box 21)
    - Personnel, Applications (Box 21)
    - Personnel, Division of (Box 21)
    - Personnel Management Information (Box 21)
    - Personnel policies and procedures (Box 21)
    - Personnel and Training, Dept. (Box 21)
    - Personnel and Training, Dept. of (Box 21)
    - Personnel, Correspondence (Box 21)
    - Pennsylvania State University (Box 21)
    - Planning and Budget, Dept. of (Box 21)
    - Planning and Budget, Dept. of (Box 21)
    - Program costs (Box 21)
    - Property Records and Insurance, Dept. of (Box 21)
    - Psychological consultants (Box 21)
    - Policy manual (Box 21)
    - Plant Pollination Advisory Board (Box 21)
    - Plant Pollination, Committee on (Box 21)
    - Public office, running for (Box 21)
    - Presidential candidates (Box 21)
    - Presidents, Advisory Council of, Finance Committee (Box 21)
    - Presidents, Advisory Council of, Personnel Committee (Box 21)
    - Presidents, Advisory Council of (Box 21)
    - Presidents, Advisory Council of, Meeting (Box 21)
    - Presidents, Advisory Council of, Meeting (Box 21)
    - Presidents, Advisory Council of, Meeting (Box 21)
    - Presidents, Advisory Council of, Meeting (Box 21)
    - Presidents, Advisory Council of, Meeting (Box 21)
    - Presidents, Advisory Council of, Meeting (Box 22)
    - Presidents, Advisory Council of, Wives letters (Box 22)
    - Privacy Protection Act (Box 22)
    - Purchase and Supply, Dept. of (Box 22)
    - Questionnaires, surveys, etc. (Box 22)
    - R, Miscellaneous (Box 22)
    - Ramsey, Robert R. (Box 22)
    - Regionalism of Post secondary Education (Box 22)
    - Rehabilitation Act of 1973 (Box 22)
    - Reports (Box 22)
    - Research and Planning, National Council for (Box 22)
    - Research reports (Box 22)
    - Resource Center and Archives (Box 22)
    - Retail Merchants Association of Greater Richmond (Box 22)
    - Retirement System, Virginia (Box 22)
    - Robertson, Col. J.W. Peyton (Box 22)
    - Rotary Club (Box 22)
    - S, Miscellaneous (Box 22)
    - Salaries (Box 22)
    - Savings Bond Campaign (Box 22)
    - SCATS Directory (Box 22)
    - SCHEV, Automated Data Procedure Committee (Box 22)
    - SCHEV, GPAC (General Professional Advisory Committee), Consolidated Salary Authorization Study (Box 22)
    - SCHEV, GPAC, General correspondence (Box 22)
    - SCHEV, GPAC, General correspondence (Box 22)
    - SCHEV, GPAC, Meetings (Box 22)
    - SCHEV, GPAC, Meetings (Box 22)
    - SCHEV, GPAC, Meetings (Box 22)
    - SCHEV, GPAC, Meetings (Box 22)
    - SCHEV, General correspondence (Box 22)
    - SCHEV, General correspondence (Box 22)
    - SCHEV, Community College System Advisory Committee (Box 22)
    - SCHEV, Continuing Education Advisory Committee (Box 22)
    - SCHEV, Advisory Committee on Education for Health Professions and Occupations (Box 22)
    - SCHEV, Advisory Committee on Education for Health Professions and Occupations (Box 22)
    - SCHEV, Advisory Committee on Education for Health Professions and Occupations (Box 22)
    - SCHEV, Advisory Committee on Education for Health Professions and Occupations (Box 22)
    - SCHEV, Council notes (Box 22)
    - SCHEV, Advisory Committee on Education for Health Professions and Occupations (Box 23)
    - SCHEV, Advisory Committee on Education for Health Professions and Occupations (Box 23)
    - SCHEV, Advisory Committee on Education for Health Professions and Occupations (Box 23)
    - SCHEV, Advisory Committee on Education for Health Professions and Occupations (Box 23)
    - SCHEV, Advisory Committee on Education for Health Professions and Occupations (Box 23)
    - SCHEV, Advisory Committee on Education for Health Professions and Occupations (Box 23)
    - SCHEV, FIPSE (Fund for the Improvement of Post-Secondary Education) (Box 23)
    - SCHEV, Facilities Utilization Subsystem (Box 23)
    - SCHEV, Finance Advisory Committee (Box 23)
    - SCHEV, General Professional Advisory Committee, Meeting (Box 23)
    - SCHEV, General Professional Advisory Committee, Meeting (Box 23)
    - SCHEV, GPAC Enrollment correspondence (Box 23)
    - SCHEV, Grade Inflation (Box 23)
    - SCHEV, IPAC (Box 23)
    - SCHEV, Letters of intent (Box 23)
    - SCHEV, Meeting (Box 23)
    - SCHEV, Nursing Manpower Advisory Committee (Box 23)
    - SCHEV, Nursing Manpower Study (Box 23)
    - SCHEV, Off Campus Advisory Committee (Box 23)
    - SCHEV, Post secondary Education Advisory Committee (Box 23)
    - Scottish Rite News, Publication (Box 23)
    - Semester system (Box 23)
    - Service Learning Centers (Box 23)
    - Servicemen's Opportunity College (Box 23)
    - Shenandoah College and Conservatory of Music (Box 23)
    - Shipp, Jim (Box 23)
    - Social Security Account Numbers, Use of (Box 23)
    - Social Security Account Numbers, Use of (Box 23)
    - Soil and Water Conservation Districts, Virginia Association (Box 23)
    - SACS (Southern Association of Colleges and Schools) (Box 23)
    - SACS (Box 23)
    - SACS (Box 23)
    - SACS (Box 23)
    - SACS, Annual meeting (Box 23)
    - SACS, Annual meeting (Box 23)
    - SACS, Special Project Dr. Hamel's office (Box 24)
    - SACS, Annual meeting (Box 24)
    - SACS, Annual meeting (Box 24)
    - SACS, Annual meeting (Box 24)
    - SREB (Southern Regional Board of Education) (Box 24)
    - Special Training (Box 24)
    - Special Training (Box 24)
    - Special Training Division Itinerary (Box 24)
    - State Agency Auxiliary (Box 24)
    - State Agency Head (Box 24)
    - State Board of Education (Box 24)
    - State Fair (Box 24)
    - State Library, Virginia (Box 24)
    - State Police, Dept. of (Box 24)
    - Stevenson, Robert D. (Box 24)
    - Student legal rights (Box 24)
    - Student loan program (Box 24)
    - Student services, Dean of (Box 24)
    - Surveys, Business and Industry (Box 24)
    - T, Miscellaneous (Box 24)
    - Taylor, Joseph M. (Box 24)
    - Taxation, Dept. of (Box 24)
    - Teacher Education, Advisory Committee on (Box 24)
    - Teaching and research positions (Box 24)
    - Telephones (Box 24)
    - Telecommunications Council (Box 24)
    - Transcript fees (Box 24)
    - Tidewater Area Health Education Committee II Study (Box 24)
    - Transfer students (Box 24)
    - Treasury, Dept. of (Box 24)
    - Tri-City Triangle (Box 24)
    - Tuition (Box 24)
    - Unions (Box 24)
    - United Nations Day (Box 24)
    - United Way Campaign (Box 24)
    - University of Florida (Box 24)
    - V, Miscellaneous (Box 24)
    - Veterans Administration (Box 24)
    - VAAHP (Virginia Association of Allied Health Professions) (Box 24)
    - Veterinary Medical Association (Box 24)
    - Virginia Air National Guard (Box 24)
    - Virginia Alcohol Safety Action Program (Box 24)
    - Virginia Association of Colleges, Meeting (Box 24)
    - Virginia Association of Collegiate Registrars and Administrative Offices (Box 24)
    - Virginia Association of Community College Faculty (Box 24)
    - Virginia Association of Continuing Education for Health Professions (Box 24)
    - Virginia Association of Student Financial Aid Administrators (Box 24)
    - Virginia Conference on Education (Box 24)
    - Virginia Correctional Enterprises (Box 24)
    - Virginia Education Association (Box 25)
    - Virginia Forms Management Program (Box 25)
    - Virginia General laws Subcommittee (Box 25)
    - Virginia Information Program (Box 25)
    - Virginia Intermont College (Box 25)
    - Virginia Municipal League (Box 25)
    - Virginia Museum (Box 25)
    - V.P.I. New Horizons Community College Conference (Box 25)
    - Virginia Recreation and Park Society (Box 25)
    - Virginia Safety Action Program (Box 25)
    - Virginia Soil and Water Conservation Commission (Box 25)
    - Vocational Act (Box 25)
    - University of Virginia (Box 25)
    - V.P.I. and S.U. (Box 25)
    - Virginia State College (Box 25)
    - Vocational Guidance Quarterly publication (Box 25)
    - Vocational Guidance Quarterly publication (Box 25)
    - Vocational-Technical Education (Box 25)
    - Vocational Education, Correspondence (Box 25)
    - Vocational Education, National Advisory Council on (Box 25)
    - Volunteerism Activities (Box 25)
    - W, Miscellaneous (Box 25)
    - Washington and Lee University speech (Box 25)
    - Washington and Lee University speech (Box 25)
    - Water Control Board, State (Box 25)
    - Western Region Consortium for Continuing Higher Education (Box 25)
    - Westmoreland, Rachel (Box 25)
    - Who's Who Among Students (Box 25)
    - Woodrow Wilson Rehabilitation Center (Box 25)
    - William and Mary, College of (Box 25)
  - Subseries C. 1978
    - AACJC (American Association of Community and Junior Colleges) (Box 26)
    - Academic and Student Affairs (Box 26)
    - Academic and Student Affairs (Box 26)
    - Administrative Affairs (Box 26)
    - Administrative Affairs (Box 26)
    - Administration and Finance, Secretary of (Box 26)
    - Advisory Council of President's Meeting (Box 26)
    - Advisory Council of President's Meeting (Box 26)
    - Advisory Council of President's Meeting (Box 26)
    - Advisory Council of President's Meeting (Box 26)
    - Advisory Council of President's Meeting (Box 26)
    - Advisory Committee on Health Professions and Occupations (Box 26)
    - Affirmative Action (Box 27)
    - Annual meeting (Box 27)
    - Annual meeting (Box 27)
    - Annual meeting (Box 27)
    - Annual reporting schedule (Box 27)
    - Applications (Box 27)
    - Apiculture program (Box 27)
    - Appalachian State University (Box 27)
    - Appendix "M" Subcommittee (Box 27)
    - Appropriations Committee (Box 27)
    - Appointment proposal (Box 27)
    - Articulation agreements (Box 27)
    - Architectural barriers (Box 27)
    - Architects and Engineers (Box 27)
    - Assistant Attorney General (Box 27)
    - Assistant Attorney General (Box 27)
    - Attorney General (Box 27)
    - Audio-Visual (Box 27)
    - Auditor of Public Accounts (Box 27)
    - Auxiliary Enterprises Operation (Box 27)
    - Bond Issue (Box 27)
    - Budget (Box 27)
    - Budget (Box 27)
    - Budget (Box 27)
    - Budget (Box 27)
    - Budget (Box 27)
    - Budget (Box 27)
    - Budget (Box 27)
    - Budget (Box 28)
    - Budget (Box 28)
    - Budget (Box 28)
    - Budget (Box 28)
    - Business-Industry Film (Box 28)
    - Business Affairs and Planning (Box 28)
    - Affirmative Action Plan, Tidewater (Box 28)
    - Capital Outlay, Priority Group by SCHED (Box 28)
    - Capital Outlay, Priorities (Box 28)
    - Capital Outlay, Thomas Nelson Community College Executive Tower (Box 28)
    - Capital Outlay, Region 22 (Norfolk, Portsmouth, Chesapeake, Virginia Beach) (Box 28)
    - Capital Outlay, Regional files miscellaneous (Box 28)
    - Capital Outlay, Tidewater Area Study Commission (Box 28)
    - The Chronicle of Higher Education (publications) (Box 29)
    - Capital Outlay (Box 30)
    - Cardio-Pulmonary resuscitation (Box 30)
    - Central Va. Educational TV (Box 30)
    - Central Va. Consortium (Box 30)
    - Chamber of Commerce, Virginia (Box 30)
    - Chamber of Commerce, Virginia (Box 30)
    - Chancellor's Faculty Advisory Committee Meeting (Box 30)
    - Chancellor's Faculty Advisory Committee Meeting (Box 30)
    - Chancellor's Faculty Advisory Committee Meeting (Box 30)
    - Chancellor's Faculty Advisory Committee Meeting (Box 30)
    - Christopherson, Charles A. (Box 30)
    - Chronicle of Higher Education, Correspondence (Box 30)
    - Civil Rights, Office of (Box 30)
    - Comptroller, Office of (Box 30)
    - Community College Policies (Box 30)
    - Computers - H.P. Fact Finding Sub-Committee (Box 30)
    - Community College Review (Box 30)
    - Conference Calls, Presidents (Box 30)
    - COPA (Council on Post secondary Accreditation) (Box 30)
    - Enrollments, Miscellaneous (Box 30)
    - Financial report, Year ending (Box 30)
    - Financial reports (Box 30)
    - General Assembly (Box 30)
    - General Assembly (Box 30)
    - Health Professions and Occupations meeting (Box 31)
    - Health Professions and Occupations meeting (Box 31)
    - Health Professions and Occupations meeting (Box 31)
    - Health Professions and Occupations meeting (Box 31)
    - GPAC (General Professional Advisory Committee) Meeting (Box 31)
    - SCHEV-GPAC Meeting (Box 31)
    - GPAC Meeting (Box 31)
    - GPAC Meeting (Box 31)
    - General Services, Dept. of (Box 31)
    - Invoices (Box 31)
    - Intergovernmental Affairs (Box 31)
    - IPAC (Instructional Programs and Advisory Committee) (Box 31)
    - JLARC (Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission) (Box 31)
    - M.B.O. Reports (Box 31)
    - Professors and Unions (Box 31)
    - Programs evaluation, Guidelines for Local College Boards (Box 31)
    - Salaries (Box 31)
    - Salary Disclosure Policy (Box 31)
    - Salary, Authorized Faculty Averages (Box 31)
    - Senate Finance Committee (Box 31)
    - Senate Document 11 (Box 31)
    - Senate Joint Resolution No. 58 (Box 31)
    - Senatorial Districts (Box 31)
    - Senators and Congressmen (Box 31)
    - Service Awards (Box 31)
    - Senate Bill No. 520 (Box 31)
    - Schewel Committee Public Hearing (Box 31)
    - The School Law newsletter (Box 31)
    - SACS (Southern Association of Colleges and Schools), Meeting (Box 31)
    - SACS, Meeting (Box 31)
    - SACS, Meeting (Box 31)
    - SREB (Southern Regional Educational Board), Correspondence (Box 31)
    - SACS, Personnel policies and procedures (Box 32)
    - SACS, Conference (Box 32)
    - SACS, Conference (Box 32)
    - SACS, Conference (Box 32)
    - SACS, Conference (Box 32)
    - SACS, Education Improvement Program (Box 32)
    - SREB (Southern Regional Education Board), Conference (Box 32)
    - SREB, Conference (Box 32)
    - SREB, Annual Report (Box 32)
    - State Board of Nursing (Box 32)
    - State Corporation Commission (Box 32)
    - SCHEV, Ad Hoc Committee (Box 32)
    - SCHEV, Reporting (Box 32)
    - SCHEV, Correspondence (Box 32)
    - SCHEV, Correspondence (Box 32)
    - SCHEV, Salary Committee (Box 32)
    - SCHEV, Health Profession and Occupation Committee meeting (Box 32)
    - SCHEV, Actions (Box 32)
    - SCHEV, Programs proposed (Box 32)
    - Southern Higher Education Legislative report (Box 32)
    - SCHEV, Health Professions and Occupations meeting (Box 33)
    - SCHEV, Correspondence (Box 33)
    - Information processing master plan (Box 33)